# **NOBLE JONES S**

joecyber114@gmail.com | +91 6374248615 |

https://www.linkedin.com/in/noble-jones-1357a8243

### **CAREER SUMMARY:**

Experienced in Security Operations Center, having worked with various SIEM solutions. Currently, handling Endpoint Detection and Response (EDR) with CrowdStrike, as well as incident handling and response. Additionally experienced in Network VAPT (Vulnerability Assessment and Penetration Testing)

### **WORK EXPERIENCE:**

# Necurity Solution Network security Pvt Ltd, India, Tamil Nadu, Chennai

SOC Analyst | Nov, 2023 - Present

- Conduct proactive monitoring and investigation of security incidents through CrowdStrike with machine learning to protect the organization against threats.
- Perform root cause analysis and provide mitigation steps to strengthen the organization's reputation.
- Provide reports and metrics to management as needed.
- Involve in network VAPT activities to identify vulnerabilities and remediate them, aiming to protect the network and assets.

## Cyberfort Fortifying Digital Security Solution Pvt Ltd India, Tamil Nadu, Chennai

Associate security consultant | Apr, 2023 - Nov, 2023

- Worked in Security Information and Event Management (SIEM) as an L1 analyst.
- Responsibilities included monitoring security events, analyzing and correlating data, prioritizing incidents, investigating, and closing tickets

#### **INTERNSHIP:**

### Penger Advertising, India, Tamil nadu, Chennai

Cyber Security Analyst | Aug 2022 - Oct 2022

- Conducted comprehensive vulnerability assessments using tools such as Nmap and Nessus.
- Identified and analyzed the vulnerabilities in the network infrastructure.
- Assisted in developing a security thesis, analyzing findings, and presenting the report to Team Leader.

### **WORKSHOP:**

- Participated in a workshop on "Cyber Security Issues and Trends" conducted in Nov 2022 by the Center for Forensic & Information Security (CCFIS)
- Participated in a workshop on "Skill Development" conducted in Oct 2019 by Infoziant IT Solution Pvt. Ltd.

#### **CERTIFICATION:**

- CEH V11 Certified Ethical hacker in EC- Council ID: (ECC8716059324)
- CSA Certified SOC Analyst in EC Council ID: (ECC0638145927)
- ISO 27001 Information Security Associate in Skill Front ID: (65280058984461)
- CSP Cyber security professionals in Fortinet

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS:**

- Function: Incident handling, proactive monitoring, network vulnerability assessment, remediation of vulnerabilities, reporting.
- Security Operations Center Tools: CrowdStrike, Splunk, Wazuh, FortiAnalyzer, Symantec.
- VAPT Tools: Nmap, Burp Suite, Nessus.
- Fundamental Knowledge: Excel, PowerPoint, Word.

### **EDUCATION:**

2019 - 2023 | DR.MGR Education and Research Institute

B.Tech in computer science and engineering specialized in

Information security and digital forensics.